

Skills

- ✓ Event Execution
- ✓ P&L Management
- √ Vendor Management
- ✓ BusinessDevelopment
- ✓ Account Management
- ✓ Brand Marketing
- ✓ Reseller Marketing

Language Proficiency

- ✓ English Native
- ✓ Hindi Expert
- ✓ Spanish Beginner

Extra-Curricular

Guest Lecturer Marketing and Sales –

St Francis Institute of Management and Research

Certified Brand Auditor

- ✓ Bare International
- ✓ Onion Insights

Brand Associations

- ✓ Accor Hotels
- ✓ Levi's
- ✓ Hyundai
- ✓ Bo-Concept
- ✓ KFC

Roydon Pinto

Result driven professional with 6 years of experience in Marketing and Business Development. Curated and executed 30+ events with Grand Hyatt, Daigeo, United Breweries, Qatar Airways, BMW Motors, etc. across 19 cities for the Times Media Network.

Work Experience

Sr Key Account Manager

Sept 2021 - June2022

PazCare InsureTech

Location - Mumbai

- Curated B2B marketing campaigns to generate qualified leads
- Sponsored & participated in Trade Shows to network with key decision makers
- Managed a team of three Junior Sales Executives and two Business Development Representatives
- Contributed to the company's Top Line Business by INR 2 Cr from Mumbai Region
- Successfully Acquired 16 New Accounts with average revenue of INR 20 Lacs Per Year
- Build and managed the complete Reseller Agent Network
- Level of client interaction- CFO, Finance Controller, Finance
 Manager, Co-Founders, HR Head, HR Manager, Purchase Head, etc.

Account Manager Brand Activations

Mar 2019 - Feb 2021

Radio Mirchi – (Times of India Group)

Location – Mumbai

- Curated and executed ad campaigns across digital, radio and BTL activations in diverse Sectors like FMCG, Auto, Real-Estate, Consumer Goods, BFSI, etc.
- Managed and executed P&L for six intellectual properties owned by Radio Mirchi across 19 cities
- Created 3 new intellectual properties for Radio Mirchi, each generating average revenue of INR 50 Lacs P.A.
- Managed Alliances with successful IP owners to collaborate and increase Top Line Business for Times of India Group.
- End-to-end vendor selection and management to aid the execution of on-ground and digital events
- Clients worked with Tata Croma, BMW, Jawa Motors, Honda Cars, Maruti Suzuki, Kingfisher, TATA AIG, Oriental Insurance, Rine Bars, Hell Energy, etc.
- Level of client interaction CMO, Brand Manager, Marketing Manager, Marketing Agency.

Key Account Specialist – Enterprise Sales

May 2017 - Mar 2019

Zeta Tech

Location Mumbai

- Acquired new business accounts under the Zeta digital benefits platform with an average of \$3
 CAC per user
- Managed existing enterprise accounts and increased the revenue per account via up-selling of additional services
- Collaborated with organizations with similar Target Group to cross market products.
- Contributed 21 new account acquisitions with average revenue of INR 8 Lacs per month
- Achieved 400% of Target and awarded Best Business Development Rep All India Level
- Level of client interaction: CHRO, CFO, Taxation, and Legal
- Clients worked with- TATA AIA, Croma, UBS, Box 8, Sharekhan, 9X Media, J.Kumar Infra, Tikona, Kodak, Donear Industries Ltd, HRI, amongst others.

Intern Corporate Sales

May 2016 - Aug 2016

Zeta Tech

Location – Mumbai

- Identified B2B prospects helping employees save Taxes under IT Tax Rules of India
- Mapped DMUs to have a broad reach of the prospects
- Conducted demos for Zeta SAAS platform on avenues of Tax Saving Mechanism
- Completed all necessary contractual obligations to onboard client
- Delivered onboarding presentations to employees in company town halls and conferences
- Ensured deliverables as per contract are met and provided ongoing after-sales support
- Overachieved set target by 126% in 3 Months
- Awarded with a Pre-Placement Offer

Case Manager – Consultant

May 2013 - Sept 2014

UGAM Solutions – Merkle Group

Location Mumbai

- Analyzed the data received for the ScreenWise Panel, a project by Google
- Assisted the clients in resolving issues faced while responding to the survey questionnaire
- Troubleshooting the issues faced by customers while using the company's devices (Laptops, routers & Internet).
- Was awarded a certificate of appreciation for my consistency in quality during my stint with the organization

Educational Qualifications

Degree	Institute	Passing Year
PGDM – MBA in Marketing	St Francis Institute of	2015-2017
	Management & Research	
Masters of Commerce	University of Mumbai	2015-2017
Bachelors of Commerce	St Andrew's College of Art's	2012-2015
	Science and Commerce	

Contact - +971 52 344 9806

Linkedin

Email - roypin321@gmail.com